aaregistry.org 2009-06-26

# African American Registry -- Your Source for African American History

Please note that African American Registry’s privacy practices as described below do not apply to the privacy policies or practices of other African American Registry’s affiliates.

Privacy Policy for Information Use at this Website

**COLLECTION AND USE OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION**

The African American Registry’s website uses cookies. A “cookie” is a small text file that contains a string of alphanumeric characters. There are two types of cookies that may be used at the aaregistry.org website: a persistent cookie and a session cookie. A persistent cookie gets entered by your Web browser into the “Cookies” folder on your computer and remains in this “Cookies” folder after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. A session cookie is held temporarily in your computer’s memory and disappears after you close your browser or shut off your computer. The African American Registry’s website may also use Web beacons (also called “clear GIFs” or “pixel tags”) in conjunction with cookies. Web beacons are small strings of code that are placed in a Web page.

If you have arrived at this website by clicking on a banner ad, a session cookie may be used. This cookie will contain an identification number for the ad that you clicked on, or will contain an identification number for the site that you were visiting when you clicked on the banner ad. This session cookie helps African American Registry’s Marketing Department determine which of our ads attract the most visitors. If, after you arrive at our site, you choose to request further information from us about us the personal information that you provide in that request will be linked to the information in the session cookie. This also helps African American Registry’s Marketing Department measure the effectiveness of our advertising. This “linking” will not be used to target future advertisements to you or to send you emails about future goods and services. You will receive emails only if you tell us that you want us to send them to you. Because this is a session cookie, it will disappear once you have closed your browser. If you return to our site via another one of our ads, you will appear as a new visitor unless and until you provide further personal information.

The African American Registry’s website may use persistent cookies, Web beacons and information collected in our log files (such as Internet Protocol Address, referring URLs, etc.) about your activity at this site to better understand how the website is used, resolve technical problems, and enhance your experience at this site. Information from website analysis cookies or about website usage is not combined with information from any other African American Registry cookie. We use a third-party email technology to send emails that you have agreed to receive. Web beacons are used in those email messages to measure the effectiveness of our advertising. If you would like to stop receiving African American Registry’s emails to which you have subscribed, please let us know.

**INFORMATION SHARING OR DISCLOSURE**

In the event that we contract with a third party to provide some part of the information or service that you have requested, African American Registry may provide your information to such third party, or such third party may collect information from you on our behalf. By written agreement, these third parties are required to implement similar security measures and to process your information only as authorized by African American Registry to fulfill the service(s) that they have been contracted to provide. Other than these entities, who act on our behalf, information you provide at this site will not be transferred to unrelated third parties, unless we have your permission to do so. However, please note that personal information provided to this site may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants or orders.

**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**

African American Registry has implemented reasonable security measures in order to protect both personal and non-personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Our employees are made aware of and are accountable for compliance with these procedures.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may amend this privacy policy from time to time as we add new services, as we improve our current offerings, and as technologies change. If we make any material or substantive changes in our treatment of information collected at this site (aaregistry.org), we will notify you by posting a clear and conspicuous notice of these changes on our website and in this privacy policy.

**CHANGES IN ORGANIZATIONAL STRUCTURE**

If all or part of the Registry is sold, merged or otherwise transferred to another entity, the information that you have provided at this site may be transferred as part of that transaction. However, African American Registry will take reasonable steps to assure that such information is used in a manner consistent with the African American Registry’s privacy policy under which it was collected.

**OTHER AFRICAN AMERICAN REGISTRY WEBSITES**

African American Registry reserves the right to use such information for sister websites owned and operated by the African American Registry. All privacy policies will continue to be upheld in regards to additional websites and all information will be held secure.
